My name is Asnakech Thomas. I come from Ethiopia.
My testimony starts like this: First of all, Good Morning, Church!
Good Morning, Church!
In 2011, I had a tummy like a barrel. I thought it was not pregnancy; that was for sure.
When I went to the hospital, they said that I was having a fibroid and needed to undergo an operation.
Then, I went to my friend. She said to me, "Don't have an operation, go to SCOAN".
So, I came to The SCOAN. I actually had to go to the overflow.
I prayed there and also received the Morning Water.
Then I went back home. I sprayed the Morning Water on myself and also drank it.
In 2012, I went for a checkup at the hospital and they still said I needed to have an operation. I said, "No".
In 2013, I didn't even bother to go to the hospital. I was just praying and praying
and everything, to my surprise, just disappeared.
This is what you see me now.
We really want to understand your testimony.
You said, after you came here... First of all, what conviction did you have to come here
after your friend told you, "No, don't go for an operation! Go to The SCOAN and get the Morning Water!"
What convinced you to just come all the way from your country to The SCOAN?
Was it like you watched your screen and your faith was encouraged?
What encouraged you to come down and get the Morning Water?
When my friend told me about The SCOAN, I didn't have the channel.
But then I bought the cable and installed it in my house.
As far as in my farm - by the way, I am a farmer.
I also got it installed on my farm, since I am a farmer.
Watching Emmanuel TV, coming here and collecting the Morning Water gave me strength.
And as I was praying, everything started turning around.
So, that was how I came to The SCOAN.
So, when you ministered the Morning Water on that fateful day, what did you experience?
You said it disappeared but how did it disappear? What did you experience?
Did you experience things coming out of you?
Yes, in a way. I didn't actually see something popping out
but a thick, creamy substance was coming out gradually.
It was really smelly. That was how it gradually came out completely.
Shall we put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
In 2014, I went back to the hospital to check if it was still there,
whilst knowing that God had already taken the sickness away.
They told me that nothing was there.
This is the first medical report that showed that I had a problem.
This is the last medical report which says that I have nothing whatsoever.
What was the problem again?
It was fibroid.
It was fibroid?
Yes, it was multiple fibroid.
So, the first medical report is showing that you then had multiple fibroid.
Yes.
And the second one says...
Nothing whatsoever.
- That you are free?
- Yes.
Shall we put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
That is not all.
Because I'm living in the countryside, being a farmer, I had to take the television down to the farm
to watch Emmanuel TV. We didn't have lights so I had to buy a generator.
So when I came in, we put it on and I was at the farm the whole day.
I tried very hard to succeed.
I have two kinds of farms now. I have a diary farm with 150 animals
and a coffee farm of 96 hectares of land.
When you came here, what challenges were you then having in your career?
Sickness, worry, and going here and there to hospitals.
I was always thinking of when I would go back to work.
It is a long way away - 550 km away from the main town.
I was just worrying a lot - also about the expenses at the hospitals for the treatment.
Then, I sprayed the Morning Water all over the farm as well.
I work with 7000 farmers - they are my farmers, I am their mum and we work together.
Then, God blessed me - not only with diary. This is a coffee farm.
These are prizes that I have won for the coffee.
This is how we wash the coffee.
Here are the farmers and myself in my farm.
So, your farm is booming now?
Yes, it is.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
This is not all.
I am the only female coffee producer and direct exporter from Ethiopia - my own brand.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
So now, you are one with a difference.
Yes. These is my exporter license for green bean.
This is the exporter license for roasted coffee.
This is the organic certification to America and this is the one for Europe.
This is the internationally registered certificate.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus!
I employ around 300 to 600 farmers at the coffee farm, out of which 80% are women.
We encourage the women to open their own accounts which is difficult.
But if they don't open an account, I don't pay them.
That is how I empower and work with them.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Asnakech Thomas
Morning Water Testimony
These are leaflets of my coffee and my diary farms.
At the diary farm, I have 150 animals.
Two days ago, one diary cow gave birth to twins.
Ohh!
Thank you.
This is how I support my 7000 farmers.
I give them incentives, train them on how to do the work perfectly and first class.
This is because I am known to be a seller of first-class coffee.
These trophies are for the first class, internationally.
So, these are the things the farmers learn from me as I train them.
We want to encourage you, Madam, to remember
that receiving healing and breakthrough is not the only thing you need.
You also need to cast aside your old self, your self-sufficiency, and take on the new life in Christ Jesus,
one that comes with humility and obedience to God's Word.
We pray that God will continue to order your steps, in Jesus' name.
Amen.